<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>10leej.com</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 10leej.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 08:48:35 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Nfs on Linux</title>
      <link>/setting-up-nfs-on-debian-10-buster/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 08:48:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/setting-up-nfs-on-debian-10-buster/</guid>
      <description>I feel my neckbeard growing in here. So there is a video guide I made a few months back.
Required Packages Debian/Ubuntu:
 Server Only   apt install nfs-kernel-server
  Client Only   apt install nfs-common
 CentOS/Redhat/Fedora (should come preinstalled)
 dnf install nfs-utils
 Setting up the file share There&amp;rsquo;s a few things that need done here. First things first we need to pick a directory, or make one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unemployed Again</title>
      <link>/unemployed-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 08:09:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/unemployed-again/</guid>
      <description>So last thurday I got woken up by a phone call from the temporary office I was employed with. The company I was contracted to work with elected to terminate me citing that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t following instruction from someone I never heard of.
Talk about a bad time, at this point in my life for the year 2020 I&amp;rsquo;ve spent more time unemployed, than employed and honestly life&amp;rsquo;s been rough for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Site</title>
      <link>/new-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 07:48:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/new-site/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new 10leej.com! I never really liked the old page, it was kind&amp;rsquo;ve a hacked solution I copy pasted off a random free html site.
Anyways this new website is just as fast to load as the old one as it&amp;rsquo;s really just plain text with an image or two on it. There&amp;rsquo;s no garage here, no ads, no trackers, no adsense, or anything. Have fun :)
Anyways you&amp;rsquo;ll find the same old links above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legend of the Black Swords</title>
      <link>/legend-of-the-black-swords/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 08:07:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legend-of-the-black-swords/</guid>
      <description>Interesting how things turn out right? Well in case you&amp;rsquo;re curious, I&amp;rsquo;ve been playing a lot of Dungeons and Dragons and my d&amp;amp;d games are streamed live on twitch every Saturday from 7pm to 11pm EST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Meaning of Life and Everything Is 42</title>
      <link>/the-meaning-of-life-and-everything-is-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 08:28:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-meaning-of-life-and-everything-is-42/</guid>
      <description>This is a repost, from something I wrote last year. &amp;ldquo;There may be some offensive language in this article&amp;rdquo; ~Joshua Lee, Editor/Writer 10leej.com
And for the love of all that could potentially be holy. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget your towel!
Let me show you something&amp;hellip;.
Yes, that is my hand, radio, and safety glasses. Their all a little dirty, same with this table in the lunch room where I took this photo on my cheapo smartphone.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>